Tufts University Gallery Records UA108
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tufts University Gallery Records
1969 -- 2019
1990-2011
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tufts University Art Gallery
UA108
43.2 Linear Feet 38 boxes and one oversized folder
109 Digital Object(s) 109 digital objects containing 4406 files.
This collection contains the records of the Tufts University Art Gallery.
Conditions Governing Access
University records are closed for 20 years from the date of their creation. Records older than 20 years that do not pertain to student education, staff and faculty employment and Board of Trustees records are open for research.
Records containing information related to student education, staff and faculty employment, and Board of Trustees records are closed for 75 years from the date of creation.
This collection may require review before it is available for use. Please contact DCA for further details.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred by the Tufts University Gallery, 2009-2019.
Arrangement
This collection arranged in three series: Additional accessions, 2017 accessions, and 2019 accessions.
Biographical / Historical
The Tufts University Art Gallery animates the intellectual life of the greater university community through exhibitions and programs exploring new, global perspectives on art and on art discourse. The Tufts University Art Gallery's exhibition space consists of the Tisch and Koppelman Galleries, the Remis Sculpture Court, a projection wall for short video and film works, and the Slater Concourse Gallery (Tufts' community gallery).
Scope and Contents
This collection contains office files and exhibit files of the Tufts University Art Gallery, including: grant files, foundation files, contracts, other financial information; MFA thesis and museum studies files; subject files; and loans and condition reports. The exhibit files contain slides and photographs. There are also two boxes containing mostly VHS tapes of exhibition videos and educational films, as well as unmarked VHS tapes. One of these boxes contains 2 Umatic cassettes of "A Day in Warsaw" from the International center for Jewish Film, dated 1991 and 1992 respectively.
Academic Support -- Libraries, Galleries, Archives; Curriculum and Instruction -- Student Work; Greater Boston arts; Performing Arts
- Additional accessions, 1969 -- 2012; UA108.001; 108 Digital Object(s) 108 digital objects containing 4215 files.
  - Box A Misc. Gallery info. No exhibit info, UA108-001 (Box 1)
    Conditions Governing Access
    20 years from date of creation.
    Scope and Contents
    Original box title.
  - Abraham Lincoln Brigade Archives floppy disk, 2000; UA108-002
    Open for research.
  - Box B cont. Box C 2003-2005 MFA Pinardi-Purcell, UA108-003 (Box 3)
  - Box C 2003-2005 MFAs, Pinardi, Purcell, Girl Culture, UA108-004 (Box 4)
  - Box C finish. Box F, 1992 -- 2004; UA108-005 (Box 5)
    Original box title. This box contains office and exhibit related files.
  - Box D exhibits, 1993 -- 1994; UA108-006 (Box 6)
  - Box D cont. exhibits, 1994-1995; Box E grants, thesis exhibitions, publicity files, UA108-007 (Box 7)
  - Box A cont., Box B 1950s-1981 exhibits, UA108-008 (Box 8)
  - Exhibits and office files, 1993 -- 1994; UA108-009 (Box 9)
  - Exhibits and office files, 1985 -- 1987; UA108-010 (Box 10)
  - Exhibits and office files, 1988 -- 1991; UA108-011 (Box 11)
  - Exhibits, 1992; UA108-012 (Box 12)
  - Exhibits, 1995; UA108-013 (Box 13)
  - Exhibits, 1993-1994, 1996, UA108-014 (Box 14)
  - Box F cont. exhibits; Office files, 1988 -- 2009; UA108-015 (Box 15)
  - Exhibits, 2001 -- 2007; UA108-016 (Box 16)
  - Exhibits and office files, 1997 -- 2005; UA108-017 (Box 17)
  - Pattern Language exhibit, 2005; UA108-018 (Box 18)
  - Exhibits and office files, 2005 -- 2007; UA108-019 (Box 19)
  - Exhibit files, 2006 -- 2007; UA108-020 (Box 20)
  - Interview with William Kentridge conducted by Dr. Pamela Allara, 2012; UA108-021
  - Box E cont. grants, thesis exhibitions, publicity, UA108-022 (Box 22)
  - Inventory, project, and registry documents, circa 1969-1996; Exhibit postcards and programs, UA108-023 (Box 23)
  - MFA/Museum School student records, 1990 -- 1994; UA108-024 (Box 24)
    75 years from the date of creation.
  - University Gifts of Art Committee; Artists' correspondence and publicity, 1983 -- 1999; UA108-025 (Box 25)
  - Exhibit files, office files, and development of museum studies program, 1987 -- 1999; UA108-026 (Box 26)
  - Art index; Office files, 1983 -- 1999; UA108-027 (Box 27)
  - Susan Masuoka correspondence and exhibit files, UA108-028 (Box 28)
    75 years from date of creation.
  - Cards and mailings, UA108-029 (Box 29)
  - Exhibition videos and video art (1 of 2), UA108-030 (Box 30)
  - Exhibition videos and video art (2 of 2), UA108-031 (Box 31)
  - Hiroshima/Nagasaki: The Fallout exhibit audio and video, 1998; UA108-032 (Box 32)
  - Exhibit posters, 1979 -- 1993; UA108-033 (Box Large Map Case 3 Drawer 10)
  - Attendance logs and meeting minutes, 2005-2010; Marketing files, 2004-2009, and fundraising, 1990-1991, UA108-034 (Box 34)
  - Mthethwa Crossing, 2005; UA108-035
  - Hiroshima/Nagasaki: The Fallout exhibit, 1998; Photographic documentation of exhibits; Misc. dead shows; MFA exhibits, 1994-1995, UA108-036 (Box 36)
  - Exhibits, 1993 -- 2003; UA108-037 (Box 37)
    Mostly exhibit announcements and press releases, 1993-2003. Also includes two folders related to the Somerville Arts Council.
  - Summer shows, 2004; UA108-038 (Box 38)
  - Budgets, attendance, Museum Studies program, 1987 -- 2003; UA108-039 (Box 39)
  - Pinardi the Great Game, 2004; UA108.036; 3 Digital Object(s)
  - Cut Piece, 2001; UA108.037; 8 Digital Object(s)
  - Cut Piece, 2001; UA108.038; 8 Digital Object(s)
  - Walk in Music + Speech Kabakou, 1994; UA108.039; 6 Digital Object(s)
  - Cosmic energy all music tracks, 1994; UA108.040; 7 Digital Object(s)
  - Chris Jordan – Altered States, 2007; UA108.041; 7 Digital Object(s)
  - Rosamond Purcell: Two rooms wall texts, 2003; UA108.042; 23 Digital Object(s)
  - Two rooms postcard, 2003; UA108.043; 2 Digital Object(s)
  - Warhol scans, 2007; UA108.044; 4 Digital Object(s)
  - Tufts gallery images, 2004; UA108.045; 52 Digital Object(s)
  - Art gallery sacred sites slideshow, 2007; UA108.046; 6 Digital Object(s)
  - NMW, 2006; UA108.047; 6 Digital Object(s)
  - Kabakov installation of Tisch & Koppelman, 2007--2008; UA108.048; 240 Digital Object(s)
  - Perm. Coll Images, 2008; UA108.049; 29 Digital Object(s)
  - Gifford House Book, 2005--2008; UA108.050; 36 Digital Object(s)
  - Tufts Gallery, 2008; UA108.051; 3 Digital Object(s)
  - Steve Mumford Artist's Talk, 2003; UA108.052; 15 Digital Object(s)
  - Links, 2005; UA108.053; 20 Digital Object(s)
  - Permanent Collection Notecards, 2008; UA108.054; 26 Digital Object(s)
  - Lauren_Greenfield, 2003; UA108.056; 15 Digital Object(s)
  - Lauren_Greenfield_Disk_2, 2003; UA108.057; 15 Digital Object(s)
  - Jun_Yang, 2003; UA108.058; 15 Digital Object(s)
  - Yellow Painting, 2007; UA108.059; 7 Digital Object(s)
  - Ferrara, 2007; UA108.060; 7 Digital Object(s)
  - Chris Jordan Altered States, 2007; UA108.061; 7 Digital Object(s)
  - Cut Piece, 2001; UA108.062; 8 Digital Object(s)
  - Alba D'Urbano, 2005; UA108.063; 9 Digital Object(s)
  - Alba D'Urbano, 2005; UA108.064; 9 Digital Object(s)
  - Alba D'Urbano, 2005; UA108.065; 9 Digital Object(s)
  - Alba D'Urbano, 2005; UA108.066; 9 Digital Object(s)
  - Pattern Language, 2005; UA108.067; 5 Digital Object(s)
  - Pattern Language B, 2005; UA108.068; 5 Digital Object(s)
  - Pattern Language C, 2005; UA108.069; 5 Digital Object(s)
  - Pattern Language Looped, 2005; UA108.070; 5 Digital Object(s)
  - Yoko Ono Lennon Studio One Cut Piece, 2001; UA108.071; 8 Digital Object(s)
  - Pattern Language Not Looped, 2005; UA108.072; 5 Digital Object(s)
  - Rosenthal, 2003; UA108.073; 8 Digital Object(s)
  - Juried_Summer_Exhibition, 2004; UA108.075; 78 Digital Object(s)
  - About_to_Forget, 2036; UA108.076; 5 Digital Object(s)
  - About_to_Forget_Left, 2036; UA108.077; 5 Digital Object(s)
  - About_to_Forget_Middle, 2036; UA108.078; 5 Digital Object(s)
  - Down_by_the_River, 2008; UA108.079; 9 Digital Object(s)
  - Zwelethu Mthethwa "Crossing" Disc 1, 2005; UA108.080; 7 Digital Object(s)
  - Zwelethu Mthethwa "Crossing" Disc #3, 2005; UA108.081; 7 Digital Object(s)
  - Tisch Rooftop Model, 2007; UA108.082; 15 Digital Object(s)
  - Jackie Ferrara Video Leigh Brodie, 2007; UA108.083; 7 Digital Object(s)
  - The Water NTSC Moataz Masr, 2005; UA108.084; 6 Digital Object(s)
  - Tisch Library Rooftop PPT, 2007; UA108.085; 2 Digital Object(s)
  - Ferrara-Friedberg Projects-Images, 2006--2007; UA108.086; 26 Digital Object(s)
  - Jackie Ferrara, 2006; UA108.087; 88 Digital Object(s)
  - Steven Mumford Tufts Show 41 images, 2003--2005; UA108.088; 43 Digital Object(s)
  - The Art Guys Suits Pics, 2005; UA108.089; 8 Digital Object(s)
  - The Art Guys Suits Images, 2005; UA108.090; 10 Digital Object(s)
  - Tufts University Image loan Ecke Bonk, 2005; UA108.091; 3 Digital Object(s)
  - I Am Pub Photo, 2004; UA108.092; 4 Digital Object(s)
  - Pattern Language files from Arauz, 1994--2004; UA108.093; 206 Digital Object(s)
  - Pattern Language Beuys copy, 2004; UA108.094; 2 Digital Object(s)
  - Harvard University Art Museums, 2004; UA108.095; 4 Digital Object(s)
  - Susana Delaphante Matienzo, 2013; UA108.096; 7 Digital Object(s)
  - Art Gallery CD, 2009; UA108.097; 2 Digital Object(s)
  - Final, 2009; UA108.098; 2 Digital Object(s)
  - Anne Eagle Tiff, 2008; UA108.099; 1 Digital Object(s)
  - Visual Griots of Mali, 2006; UA108.100; 50 Digital Object(s)
  - Fall 2012 installation images, UA108.101; 102 Digital Object(s)
  - Mark_Shetabi, 2008; UA108.102; 12 Digital Object(s)
  - Saira_Wasim, 2008; UA108.103; 2 Digital Object(s)
  - Lara_Baladi_2, 2008; UA108.104; 8 Digital Object(s)
  - Lara_Baladi_1, 2008; UA108.105; 9 Digital Object(s)
  - Contemp_Arts_Circle, 2008; UA108.106; 1 Digital Object(s)
  - Global_Flows_2, 2011--2012; UA108.107; 2 Digital Object(s)
  - Global_Flows_1, 2010--2013; UA108.108; 203 Digital Object(s)
  - NA_1, 2011; UA108.109; 2 Digital Object(s)
  - NA_2, 2004; UA108.110; 2 Digital Object(s)
  - Ethnog_2008, UA108.111; 8 Digital Object(s)
  - Grad Student Photos, 2010; UA108.112; 10 Digital Object(s)
  - Broadside, 2010; UA108.113; 2 Digital Object(s)
  - Passing Moods, 2005; UA108.114; 5 Digital Object(s)
  - Persian Visions, 2004; UA108.115; 18 Digital Object(s)
  - Bruce Davidson Time of Change, 2005; UA108.116; 59 Digital Object(s)
  - The Institute Yuri Makoveychuk, 2003; UA108.117; 7 Digital Object(s)
  - Tufts Art Gallery, 2010; UA108.118; 14 Digital Object(s)
  - Empathic Imagination, 2010; UA108.119; 7 Digital Object(s)
  - Seher Shah Perversios of Empire Images, 2008; UA108.120; 24 Digital Object(s)
  - Avini images, 2008; UA108.121; 48 Digital Object(s)
  - AK_Roadworks, 2010; UA108.122; 7 Digital Object(s)
  - Princess_Mononoke, 2009; UA108.123; 16 Digital Object(s)
  - Disc 2 Akira Beautiful Dreamer Ghost in the Shell Ju-on, 2009; UA108.124; 16 Digital Object(s)
  - Eyes of Others Fenmore Art Museum 5/08, 2008; UA108.125; 40 Digital Object(s)
  - Candice Smith Corby New Images, 2006; UA108.126; 30 Digital Object(s)
  - Farhad Moshiri, 2007; UA108.127; 6 Digital Object(s)
  - Andrew Rogers, 2011--2012; UA108.128; 28 Digital Object(s)
  - Mural installation, 2013; UA108.129; 10 Digital Object(s)
  - NEA Kabakov App., 2005; UA108.130; 1 Digital Object(s)
  - Equal/Opposite, 2010; UA108.131; 7 Digital Object(s)
  - Global Flows, 2013; UA108.132; 23 Digital Object(s)
  - Questions Without Answers, 2010; UA108.133; 137 Digital Object(s)
  - Terry Rosenberg, 2011; UA108.134; 3 Digital Object(s)
  - Lehman Bravo Collection, 2009; UA108.135; 57 Digital Object(s)
  - VYV Coordinator, 2007--2011; UA108.136; 2035 Digital Object(s)
  - Masako_Kamiya_Blue_Fairy, 2011; UA108.137; 90.5 Megabytes; 2
  - Preview_Copy_Ethnographgy_of_Noplace, 2009; UA108.138; 1331.2 Megabytes; 8
  - Rosamond_Purcell_Opening_Justin_Knight, 2003; UA108.139; 8.6 Megabytes; 466
  - Daniel_Jay_Market_Show_2011, 2009--2010; UA108.140; 19.3 Megabytes; 28
  - Andrew_Rogers_Rhythms_of_Life_Chyulu_Hills_Kenya_2010, 2011; UA108.141; 2252.8 Megabytes; 9
  - Finished jpegs, 2004; UA108.142; 23.6 Megabytes; 26
- 2017 accessions, circa 1996 -- 2012; UA108.002; 4.8 Linear Feet
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged in received order.
  University records are closed for 20 years from the date of creation. Records older than 20 years that do not pertain to student education, staff and faculty employment and Board of Trustees records are open for research.
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Transferred by the Tufts University Gallery, 2017, accession UA-2017-056 and UA-2017-057.
  This series contains Tufts University Art Gallery office files, including grant files, foundation files, contracts, and other financial information. This series also contains exhibition files, MFA thesis and museum studies files, and loans and condition reports.
  - CAP Grant-Keping, 2007 -- 2008; UA108.002.040.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 40)
    20 years from date of creation
    UA-2017-056
  - CAP Grant, 2010; UA108.002.040.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 40)
  - CAP Grant App, circa 2010; UA108.002.040.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 40)
  - Carl Pope, 2009; UA108.002.040.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 40)
  - Carl Pope NEA Grant, 2009 -- 2010; UA108.002.040.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 40)
  - Carl Pope-Koppelman, 2009; UA108.002.040.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 40)
  - Collection Storage, circa 2009; UA108.002.040.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 40)
  - Cricket Foundation, circa 2009; UA108.002.040.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 40)
  - Curator-Squared Contract-"Interface", circa 2010; UA108.002.040.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 40)
  - Diversity Fund, 2007 -- 2008; UA108.002.040.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 40)
  - Etant-Donnes, circa 2008; UA108.002.040.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 40)
  - Etant-Donnes Fund, circa 2008; UA108.002.040.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 40)
  - FY08 Organizational Support Final Report, 2007 -- 2008; UA108.002.040.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 40)
  - Fall 2010 Other Fundraising, UA108.002.040.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 40)
  - FedEx/UPS, circa 2010; UA108.002.040.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 40)
  - FY11 CAC Supporters, 2010 -- 2011; UA108.002.040.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 40)
  - Gallery Attendants, 2007; UA108.002.040.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 40)
  - Gallery Guide Program, circa 2007; UA108.002.040.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 40)
  - Graham Foundation, circa 2007; UA108.002.040.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 40)
  - Harpo Fund, 2009; UA108.002.040.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 40)
  - Henricks Endowment, circa 2009; UA108.002.040.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 40)
  - IMLS Conservation Project Support, circa 2009; UA108.002.040.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 40)
  - Interface/Firestone Graham Foundation, circa 2009; UA108.002.040.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 40)
  - Interface/Warhol Foundation, 2009; UA108.002.040.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 40)
  - Kabakov-AT&T Foundation, circa 2006; UA108.002.040.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 40)
  - Kabakov-Braman, circa 2006; UA108.002.040.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 40)
  - Kabakov-LEF Grant, 2006; UA108.002.040.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 40)
  - Kabakov-MAT Foundation, circa 2006; UA108.002.040.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 40)
  - Kabakov-NEA Grant, 2005; UA108.002.040.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 40)
  - Kabakov-NEA Grant, 2006; UA108.002.040.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 40)
  - Kabakov-Norton Foundation, circa 2006; UA108.002.040.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 40)
  - Kabakov-Other Fundraising/Grants, circa 2006; UA108.002.040.00032; 1 Folder(s) (Box 40)
  - Kabakov-Sloane Foundation, circa 2006; UA108.002.040.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box 40)
  - Kabakov-Warhol Foundation Grant, circa 2006; UA108.002.040.00034; 1 Folder(s) (Box 40)
  - LED Signage, circa 2007; UA108.002.040.00035; 1 Folder(s) (Box 40)
  - LEF, 2007 -- 2009; UA108.002.040.00036; 1 Folder(s) (Box 40)
  - LSI Lighting Services, circa 2009; UA108.002.040.00037; 1 Folder(s) (Box 40)
  - MAP Grant, 2007; UA108.002.040.00038; 1 Folder(s) (Box 40)
  - MAP Grant, 2009; UA108.002.040.00039; 1 Folder(s) (Box 40)
  - MAP Public Dimension Grant, circa 2009; UA108.002.040.00040; 1 Folder(s) (Box 40)
  - Mark Murphy Grants Writer, circa 2009; UA108.002.040.00041; 1 Folder(s) (Box 40)
  - Mass Cultural Council Grant, 2007; UA108.002.040.00042; 1 Folder(s) (Box 40)
  - MCC Cultural Data Project, circa 2001; UA108.002.040.00043; 1 Folder(s) (Box 40)
  - MCC, 2000 -- 2001; UA108.002.040.00044; 1 Folder(s) (Box 40)
  - MCC Grant, 2004; UA108.002.040.00045; 1 Folder(s) (Box 40)
  - MCC Grant, 2007; UA108.002.041.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - MCC Grant, 2008 -- 2010; UA108.002.041.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - MCC Grant, 2010 -- 2011; UA108.002.041.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - Mildred's Lane Contract, circa 2010; UA108.002.041.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - NEA 240, circa 2004; UA108.002.041.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - NEA, 2004; UA108.002.041.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - NEA Final Draft, 2005 -- 2006; UA108.002.041.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - NEA Grant, 2008; UA108.002.041.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - NEA Grant-Interface, 2009; UA108.002.041.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - NEA Recovery Act Application, 2009; UA108.002.041.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - NEH Preservation Grant, 2010; UA108.002.041.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - Nina Bozicnik-Voice Your Vision!, circa 2010; UA108.002.041.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - Past Part-time Staff/Temps, circa 2010; UA108.002.041.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - Pop Women-Budgets, circa 2010; UA108.002.041.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - Pop Women-Travel, circa 2010; UA108.002.041.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - Pop Women-Grant Apps, circa 2010; UA108.002.041.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - Questions Without Answers Contract, circa 2006; UA108.002.041.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - Spring 2006 Gallery Attendants, UA108.002.041.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - Voice Your Vision-Bozicnik Contract, circa 2010; UA108.002.041.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - Warhol Foundation, circa 2010; UA108.002.041.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - MFA, 2001; UA108.002.041.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
    UA-2017-057
  - Museum Studies, 2001; UA108.002.041.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - Museum Studies, 2002; UA108.002.041.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - Museum Studies-loans and condition reports, 2002; UA108.002.041.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - MFA Guidelines, January, 2002; UA108.002.041.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - MFA Thesis, May, 2002; UA108.002.041.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - MFA April-May, 2004; UA108.002.041.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - MFA December, 2004; UA108.002.041.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - MFA January, 2005; UA108.002.041.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - MFA Fall, 2005; UA108.002.041.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - Museum Studies, 2005; UA108.002.041.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - MFA April, 2005; UA108.002.041.00032; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - MFA, 2005 -- 2006; UA108.002.041.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - MFA Fall, 2006; UA108.002.041.00034; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - Museum Studies-loan forms, 2006; UA108.002.041.00035; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - Museum Studies-condition reports, 2006; UA108.002.041.00036; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - Museum Studies-misc., 2006; UA108.002.041.00037; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - Summer Show, 2007; UA108.002.041.00038; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - Jackie Ferrara: Library Roof, 2007; UA108.002.041.00039; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - Bruce Odiland Sound Project, Spring, 2008; UA108.002.041.00040; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - Juried Summer, 2008; UA108.002.041.00041; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - Slater Exhibits, 2007 -- 2008; UA108.002.041.00042; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - MFA Thesis Fall, 2008; UA108.002.041.00043; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - C. Tomaszewski Spring, 2009; UA108.002.041.00044; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - Juried Show Summer, 2009; UA108.002.041.00045; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - Loan Agreements Summer, 2009; UA108.002.041.00046; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - December MFA Thesis, 2009; UA108.002.041.00047; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - MFA Spring, 2010; UA108.002.041.00048; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - Dinh Q. Le, Shipping: Spring, 2009; UA108.002.041.00049; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - Sacred Monsters Fall, 2009; UA108.002.041.00050; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - Questions without Answers, contd Spring, 2010; UA108.002.041.00051; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - Saya Woolfalk Spring, 2010; UA108.002.041.00052; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - Walden-Puett/Dion Fall, 2010; UA108.002.041.00053; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - Mexico Beyond its Revolutions Fall, 2010; UA108.002.041.00054; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - Dec MFA, 2010; UA108.002.041.00055; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - Seductive Subversion Spring, 2011; UA108.002.041.00056; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - Mildred's Lane, circa 2011; UA108.002.041.00057; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - Summer, 2011; UA108.002.041.00058; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - Richard Bell Fall, 2011; UA108.002.041.00059; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - Ken Gonzalez Day: Profiled Fall, 2011; UA108.002.041.00060; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - Boston-Joburg, circa 2011; UA108.002.041.00061; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - Ken Gonzalez Day, circa 2011; UA108.002.041.00062; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - Bell-AFA Contract, circa 2011; UA108.002.041.00063; 1 Folder(s) (Box 41)
  - Boston-Joburg, circa 2011; UA108.002.042.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 42)
  - Dec MFA, 2011; UA108.002.042.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 42)
  - April MFA, 2012; UA108.002.042.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 42)
  - May MFA, 2012; UA108.002.042.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 42)
  - Dec MFA, 2012; UA108.002.042.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 42)
  - Boston-Joburg, circa 2012; UA108.002.042.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 42)
  - April MFA, circa 2012; UA108.002.042.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 42)
  - May MFA, circa 2012; UA108.002.042.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 42)
  - TIAA-CREFF Project-Summer, 2004; UA108.002.042.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 42)
  - Evidence-Fall, 2004; UA108.002.042.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 42)
  - Amazing & Immutable-Return Shipping Fall, 2004; UA108.002.042.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 42)
  - Yoran Wolberger (Overt/Covert) Falll, 2004; UA108.002.042.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 42)
  - "Altered States" Research, 2005; UA108.002.042.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 42)
  - Altered States-Loan Agreement Cover Letters, circa 2005; UA108.002.042.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 42)
  - Mwangi-New Media Spring, 2006; UA108.002.042.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 42)
  - Berni Searle-New Media Spring, 2006; UA108.002.042.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 42)
  - Moataz Nasr-New Media Spring, 2006; UA108.002.042.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 42)
  - Zwelethu Mthethwa-New Media Spring, 2006; UA108.002.042.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 42)
  - Kavakov Press, circa 2006; UA108.002.042.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 42)
  - Spring New Media, 2006; UA108.002.042.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 42)
  - Fall Slater Shows, 2006; UA108.002.042.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 42)
  - Jackie Ferrara-Spring, 2007; UA108.002.042.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 42)
  - Event Planning-Spring, 2007; UA108.002.042.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 42)
  - Altered States-Spring, 2007; UA108.002.042.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 42)
  - Altered States-Spring, 2007; UA108.002.042.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 42)
  - Junyang (Spring), 2007; UA108.002.042.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 42)
  - Edward Burtynski-The China Series-Spring, 2007; UA108.002.042.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 42)
  - SECCA Contract-Bertinski: The China Series (Spring), 2007; UA108.002.042.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 42)
  - Fourth Annual Juried Show (Summer), 2007; UA108.002.042.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 42)
  - Global Village Shelters (Fall), 2007; UA108.002.042.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 42)
  - VDA Contracts, Ilya and Emilia Kabakov Fall, 2007; UA108.002.042.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 42)
  - Communications Brief FAH 287 Spring, 2007; UA108.002.042.00032; 1 Folder(s) (Box 42)